Test Collection PLEASE.WORK PLEASE.WORK
Rockefeller Archive Center
Test Collection
1958-2013
Rockefeller Archive Center
PLEASE.WORK
1.2 Gigabytes
- Board Records, 1998 November 12 - 2009 April 9; 193.5 kilobytes
  Scope and Contents
  This is a comment
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Meetings, 1997-2012, 2008 September 17; 94.5 kilobytes
    - Agendas, 1998 April 27 - 2013 January 23; 1.1 Megabytes
    - Dockets, 1998 December 3 - 2013 February 6; 9.1 Megabytes
    - Meeting Materials and Notes, 2013 January 31; 32.1 Megabytes
      - 2003 December, 2003 December 1; 41.5 kilobytes
      - 2003 September, 2003 September 9; 43.0 kilobytes
      - 2004 November, 2004 November 29 - 2004 November 30; 106.5 kilobytes
      - 2005 March, 2005 March 22; 53.0 kilobytes
      - 2005 May, 2005 May 19; 47.0 kilobytes
      - 2006 April, 2006 April 11; 200.5 kilobytes
      - 2006 November, 2006 November 29 - 2006 November 30; 83.5 kilobytes
      - 2006 September, 2006 September 13; 47.0 kilobytes
      - 2007 May and December, 2007 May 22 - 2007 December 4; 94.5 kilobytes
      - 2009 December, 2009 November 24 - 2013 January 31; 1.0 Megabytes
      - 2009 May, 2009 April 13 - 2010 January 6; 959.0 kilobytes
      - 2010 December, 2010 November 9 - 2013 January 31; 10.5 Megabytes
      - 2010 May, 2010 April 12 - 2010 May 12; 7.0 Megabytes
      - 2010 September, 2010 September 9 - 2010 September 30; 1.7 Megabytes
      - 2011 December, 2011 September 15 - 2013 January 31; 16.4 Megabytes
      - 2011 March, 2009 October 30 - 2011 March 22; 18.2 Megabytes
      - 2011 May, 2011 April 8 - 2011 September 19; 2.6 Megabytes
      - 2011 September-October, 2011 June 22 - 2011 October 14; 4.8 Megabytes
      - 2012, 2011 October 25 - 2013 January 31; 22.6 Megabytes
        Materials in this file are restricted.
    - Memos, 1998 November 12 - 2013 February 4; 201.7 kilobytes
      - Bill Green Memorial, 2002 November 1 - 2005 May 13; 222.0 kilobytes
      - Cover Memos for Briefing Books, 1999 April 16 - 2010 May 3; 1.0 Megabytes
      - General, 1998 April 29 - 2009 April 9; 2.2 Megabytes
  - Minutes, 2006 April 13 - 2013 February 4; 199.2 kilobytes
    - 1997, 1997 September 26; 11.0 kilobytes
    - 1998, 1998 May 19 - 1999 May 6; 59.0 kilobytes
    - 1999, 1999 September 23 - 2000 June 23; 71.5 kilobytes
    - 2000-2005, 2000 April 24 - 2006 April 13; 768.5 kilobytes
    - 2006-2010, 2006 April 13 - 2010 November 16; 1.5 Megabytes
    - 2011-2012, 2011 May 4 - 2012 November 30; 410.7 kilobytes
- Grants: Nature Conservancy, 2004-2005, undated
- Grants: New York University School of Law, 2002 December 12; 20.7 Megabytes
- Grants: Pratt Institute, 2001, 2001 June 26; 7.6 Megabytes
- Grants: Wednesdays in Mississippi Documentary Film Project, undated
- Organization Records, 2011 December 7; 36.0 kilobytes
  - Center for Summer Learning, 2005 February 7 - 2010 July 27; 2.4 Megabytes
    File contains proposal for funding of a resource guide on summer learning programs.
  - Contracts, 2002 February 25; 28.0 kilobytes
    - Owens, Christine, 2002 December 18 - 2003 July 15; 84.5 kilobytes
      Payments for research on urban boarding schools.
    - Saegert, Susan, 2002 February 25 - 2003 September 2; 334.5 kilobytes
      Records relate to consultancy agreement with Susan Saegert to survey the literature on Limited Equity Housing Cooperatives.
  - General, 2000 March 20 - 2010 April 14; 6.3 Megabytes
    File contains vaqrious materials relating to Taconic Foundation investments and program directions. Includes material on the Poverty and Race Research Action Council, Pratt Institute Center, Smokey House, andthe Urban Homesteading Assistance Board, as well as reports on Out-of-School Time programs. File was originally labeled "Miscellaneous."
  - General Correspondence, 2000 July 26 - 2005 October 3; 640.0 kilobytes
    File consists mainly of correspondence with Jane Lee and other trustees, concerning board and foundation business; but it also includes some administrative or grant-related correspondence. Materials were originally filed under "Letter."
  - Grantmaking and Foundation History, 2009 January 7; 21.5 kilobytes
    - Fiftieth Anniversary, 2007 October 5 - 2008 September 23; 1.4 Megabytes
    - Grant Summary, 1998 November 17 - 2009 November 24; 333.0 kilobytes
      File contains annual or biannual breakdowns of grant funding by program area.
    - Grants Guidelines, 2005 January 7 - 2011 January 3; 400.5 kilobytes
      File contains statements of the funding guidelines for grant applicants.
    - Grants Lists, 2003 January 14 - 2013 January 14; 587.1 kilobytes
      Annual lists of grants, broken down by program area.
  - Oral History Project (Jan Jaffe) - 2012, 2010 December 1 - 2012 December 10; 5.1 Megabytes
  - Research Supported by Taconic, 2003 August 1; 311.0 kilobytes
    - Limited Equity Housing Cooperatives, 2002 November 12 - 2004 January 30; 1.6 Megabytes
      File contains drafts of Susan Saegert's report on Limited Equity Housing Cooperatives, and memos concerning its distribution.
      - General, 2002-2003 May, 2002 November 12 - 2003 May 28; 954.5 kilobytes
      - General, 2003 June-December, 2003 June 10 - 2003 August 1; 595.0 kilobytes
      - Paper (Distribution), 2004 January 12 - 2004 January 30; 88.5 kilobytes
    - New Markets Tax Credits, 2004 October 7 - 2006 January 5; 708.5 kilobytes
      File contains draft of and comments on Taconic-funded paper "New Markets Tax Credits: Issues and Opportunities," by P. Jefferson Armistead.
      - General, 2002-2004, 2004 October 7 - 2006 January 5; 708.5 kilobytes
      - General, 2005-2006, 2004 October 7 - 2006 January 5; 708.5 kilobytes
      - Paper, 2005 March 22; 437.0 kilobytes
  - Rockefeller Archive Center, 2012 January 13 - 2013 January 15; 1007.9 kilobytes
  - Section 8 Housing, 2005 February 19 - 2005 October 24; 1.2 Megabytes
    File contains briefing papers and other materials relating to the National Low-Income Housing Coalition's 2005 National Housing Voucher Summit. The Taconic Foundation was a cosponsor of the meeting.
  - Spend-Down Process: 2012, 2012 February 28 - 2013 January 14; 6.6 Megabytes
  - Spend-Down Process: Quo Vadimus, 2010 April 13; 200.0 kilobytes
    - Board Memos and Correspondence, 2008 March 18 - 2011 March 21; 3.2 Megabytes
      Includes memos by John Simon and Melvin Mister.
    - Four Program Memos, 2007 March 1 - 2011 January 25; 2.3 Megabytes
      File concerns possible programs within four targeted areas: Affordable Housing and Community Development, Race Relations, Social Entrepreneurship, and Youth organizations.
    - Reference Materials, 2004 August 30 - 2010 January 12; 12.2 Megabytes
      Includes Articles and Reports Consulted.
    - Survey, 2009 March 17 - 2009 March 25; 395.0 kilobytes
      The Taconic Foundation conducted a survey of grantee organizations concerning the effects of the economic downturn.
    - Write-Ups, 2009 April 17 - 2009 May 21; 649.5 kilobytes
      File contains summary statements on organizations put forward for spend-down grant funding in 2009. Includes information on their programs, funding history, sources of support, and reasons for recommending them.
  - Strategy Paper, 2013 January 23; 0 bytes
    - 1998 Megan Cole, 1998 April 27 - 2000 June 16; 92.0 kilobytes
      Materials relate to investigations of Residential Schools and Summer Learning initiatives.
    - General, 2004 January 23 - 2005 June 17; 1.1 Megabytes
      Materials date from 2004-2005 and concern Taconic's funding history and guidelines and its narrowing focus on community and youth development. In February 2004 Taconic produced its "Opportunities for Community Development: A Brief Survey for Small Foundations," as a kind of a roadmap for its program direction.
  - Taconic Foundation Reports: Three-Year Report, 1999 December 23; 63.5 kilobytes
  - Trustee Files, 2003 December 3 - 2004 September 22; 91.0 kilobytes
    - Green, Bill: General, 2002 October 15 - 2004 September 22; 156.0 kilobytes
    - Green, Bill: Memorial Lecture Series, 2002 October 15 - 2009 November 24; 1.0 Megabytes
      - Advisory Committee Minutes, 2005 October 5 - 2005 December 9; 50.0 kilobytes
      - General, 2002 October 15 - 2009 November 24; 1.0 Megabytes
      - Speaker Biographies, 2009 March 25; 753.5 kilobytes
    - Mister, Melvin A., 2007 November 13; 35.0 kilobytes
    - Trustees (General), 2005 March 16 - 2012 September 25; 174.0 kilobytes
      - Correspondence, 2004 January 14 - 2013 February 4; 247.5 kilobytes
      - Nominations, 2003 December 3 - 2004 September 22; 91.0 kilobytes